We are on there. Hello, let's see. I'm broadcasting from a new software tonight. We just make sure
Everything's good streaming resolution
We erase that
Okay, well
Don't see how to fix it. Okay. Well, anyway, hi guys, I had a few people wanting me to go on tonight, so
I decided to come on
Okay, so but this is a new software I might switch over to this one. I'm not sure
I kind of like it
But maybe it's just cuz it's new you know
Okay
Hi, here's Lenore. Hey Lenore. Oh my gosh. I'm gonna make my robes tonight. I was just in the mood
Hey Lenore, I'm gonna say hi
Hi, baby. Hi, Jamie. Yeah, you came okay good
It's Lenore. Do I look good tonight? It's 12.30. I know I'm sorry. I was a little bit slow and
I took a shower. You were waiting. I needed an hour instead of just 30 minutes. Hey Lenore.
Are you loving tonight? She's really happy because you know, I take a really good shower and then whenever I do that
I wipe all the I get all her scent off of me
And then she comes and puts it back on
You do that you do that you have to be right here. Oh, oh, you do. Oh
Oh, you like it. Oh
This is on the ears this is on the ears
Uh-oh Santa does Dallas day three the cops have been called. Oh, where were the cops called? So you were in Dallas, okay?
So Nick, are you in that movie Debbie does Dallas? Have you heard of that movie?
That was actually the first born I ever saw. Oh my god, but the story is kind of bad because I was probably way too young to be watching it
Hi, Lenore, this is Miss Lenore. Lenore, are you gonna visit Nick in jail? You gonna visit Nick in jail?
No, no. Oh, you're not gonna bail them out. Oh, that's so mean of you
Okay, so I'm just testing out some of this too. Let me see if I can share my screen
I know you probably saw some of this today. Okay, so I can share that screen. Can I can I put up like a?
File presentation. Okay
What it's not letting me do like a lot of things
I can raise my hand, okay. I can be acting out like this
Hi Lenore, I
Can oh mark my clips. Hey
No, you're just so loving
You're so loving
Want to give me kisses
Okay, well, I guess I'll just have to I can share my screen
So that's I don't have to share the actual video. I can just go from my
This was the one I did. I did a couple videos
I did one this morning, and then I did so I don't know I think Jamie spots. You know, Chona's birthday today
the birthday Chona
Okay, I like I like the oh
Shit, I like the the channel title. They figured out my banner
Okay, well anyway, let's see
This is called
They didn't play anything on the way in
I need to move this all right, okay, this is called
Secrets behind the throne, okay, see if you like this one
Okay, you see if it works
Okay, no, no, where am I? Where's my stream streaming software? Okay. Where is it? Oh my gosh
What the hell oh here it's okay, okay. Wow put the link down. Okay, so here's the link
It's different. This is not stream yard. It's a different site. Okay, but it should be just as easy
So go ahead try that one
Share screen
Higher screen actually I can just do the tabs. Okay, so it's the secrets behind the throne. Yeah, you're welcome
Oh
I was born where the whisper shake hands with the throne
Halo been crooked, but the crown is my own
City sees a savior, back room sees a sin
Everybody swears they know me, no one's been with them
They want the man, they want the mask, they want the fall
They pray I break just to prove I'm not Marvel at all
But I learned my power
the lights go to drown in the hush of the scandal
i force the shadow crown they project their hunger they accuse they adore
same lips that kiss the ring beg to kick in the door
i wear the shadow
They sharpen their r-
the shadow of crime.
There you go.
Alright, so I don't know if it did it that well.
Excuse me?
Excuse me? What? What? What? Who's crying about what?
Don't care. No, you don't have to sign up. No, it's just the same as um, it's the same as dream yard
See, all you have to do is just go in and just go in the studio
It's the same thing
Yeah, it's easy. I know it's different. I'm not crying. I don't care if I
I'm cool without guests tonight. Oh shit. My father's psyche here. I'm gonna always in a good mood. Hey, Sipha. How are you?
And if you guys if you're not modded, I just so I can't see them
Mods through this one. Hey, Gotti
Hey, what's up?
Good to see you
Okay, while we wait for people to come up
I'm sick. I just want to show you the videos I made today. I mean
Didn't do one more. I did one more. I actually did two more, but I'll play the one I animated myself
Let me see if this even okay
This one's called Aquarian Exile. Okay, so that one that what I just played was based on my astrology
It's called the shadow crown because I have this like stellium. I think it's called stellium. It was like all these placements and like
Kind of like the dark place of my chart. It's like where my Lilith is right there and I got my Pluto's right there
But then my Jupiter and Saturn are right there, too. And so it says
It's kind of a shadow crown. Okay, so let's see. Bye
Can do this a share screen. Oh, there it goes
This is something wrong now I'm getting up. Oh, ah, how'd you get up here?
Just let you up automatically, the fuck?
I need to fix this thing.
See, how are you?
Oh, where'd he go?
Where'd he go?
Did I see SIG?
What's going on here?
Hold on.
Where'd he go?
Was SIG just here?
Did you just see SIG?
Your wrench is gone?
I don't know.
I'll give it back to you.
Hold on.
Did anyone see SIG there?
Or am I just kidding?
Am I hallucinating?
I think I just saw SIG.
He just, like, was here.
Did you see him I?
Don't know what that was that's weird. I don't like how it's just like someone just came up here
Hi, hey oceans. Woo. How are you? Oh?
Okay, you ran to see if I thought hey
And everyone you know can we please be respect everyone just be respectful tonight?
I don't want to like you know nobody be rude just like come on
Let's let's treat people like we're gonna be treated okay. I was gonna show this little video
I mean, so guys are you behaving yourself behave yourself guys?
You can see it, okay
I learned the shape of alone before I learned your name
Not the lonely kind, the necessary, famous are the cases, and the promises they make.
Smile stitched tight just to keep people tame, they said.
Standing line, pick a side, choose a rope.
But the future was knocking, hosin' my soul.
I took three steps left, and I stayed right there.
Close enough to see it far enough to not care.
They movin' circles, I'm movin' arcs, they trade their poles.
For a place in the dark
I read your rooms like a storm on the way
I hear the knots in the words you don't say
You call it genius, you call it strange
But exile just means I won't be trained
I watch the herd trade breakfast
Someone see me and I need me to be a king
I'm tired of being fragments you admire in parts
I want a mirror that doesn't take me apart
chest on fire saying rule with your heart not just your wire saying you
don't have to die just to stay free saying they don't need a ghost they
need you see
I don't know that, I don't know that,
why am I so old at the end?
That was the reveal, I was like an old man
with a really big beard.
Wow.
Yeah, it's Riverside, it's Riverside.
I don't know, can you guys get on?
I don't know, did anybody see Sig come up?
Like, I saw him like in the studio, I think, with me.
And I was like, what the hell?
And then he disappeared.
Did you see that?
Anybody see that?
No one's to come up on reverse side, okay.
Well, the same thing as StreamYard is like the exact same thing.
It even looked easier than StreamYard to get on.
Why don't you try it?
Because StreamYard is raising its price $20 this month.
Yeah, that's what I'm buying.
You like that?
I made that this morning.
I'm getting kind of good at, like, I can,
I do a storyboard kind of thing.
I generate the images and then I animate them and then I edit it all together
So it is kind of a labor-intensive, but I really enjoy the result, you know, so
Yeah, that's one of mine
I
Don't know. I don't know. What's wrong with streamer? Oh, yeah, they're raising the price $20. They're raising the price $20. Nothing's wrong with it
I'm just I'm just testing this out. It's actually got some cool features and stuff. I don't know why I don't know
You don't have to be scared of it. It's like I can go like this actually on it watch
you're like that okay well do you want to hear another song uh this one's called baby girl
i just like the uh well it's a good song actually
it's not like edited that as well as the other one i did it quick but um i did put a little
glitching effect into it so it maybe like it looks a little better okay there we go share
Yes, it's good actually is it yeah, I think you like it
Breadstain, mouth confession, why you step through hell like it's divine
Velvet voice with venom, grin, you say I'm in, then drag me in
You wanna love that scars the soul, you don't want one, you want control
Glass build skin, typhoon inside, you kiss like prophecy, light like fate
you don't ask for saving you some in the fall like a handcuffed on a prison wall
everywhere cuts reach you deep a promise you'll never keep
baby girl don't crown the flame it'll burn your throne
and wear your name you want the aim you want the chain you
Stay
Sway bigger
Kiss is a binding spell
You keep circling your private hell
I'm the shadow you can undo
The truth that keeps finding you
Baby girl, don't close your sight
I want your dreams like
Yo, what's up?
Yo, can you hear me? Yeah, I don't know what the fuck this fucking space-age shit is no fence
I'm just trying to like this is like some NASA shit. I'm not like I don't know what's going on
Some NASA shit Alex I'm about to ban you I don't care. I don't care Alex. I'm about to ban you seriously
Fucking annoying me. I don't care Alex
I'm come like what's going on here. Why are you? What is this? I've never even heard of this. What is this?
well, I'm on like a free I think a 14 day free premium on channel of it and
Yeah, it's not TV stream art. It actually has more stuff than stream art. It actually has some better stuff
But this one's like $20 cheaper
And uh, there's like five bucks a month. No, no, no, I because I was at $25 on a stream yard
And now they're raising it back to 45 because I like I'm just a specific amount of time I could do that
Yeah, this is it's owned by like the Russians
Well, I don't know it's like but you know it
It works kind of the same no offense the Russians, but like yeah
That's fine. I mean, I think it looks good. I like I like how the camera looks and stuff
I had a Russian girlfriend before and she was great. She was really nice, but like her family didn't like me. Oh
Like they were like, oh like they're like they like why are you talking to this guy? Oh
with a racist I
Mean, I guess you could say that
Well, hey Alex
I'm really gonna kick you out. I'll just tie me up for 24 hours. Where are the comments? I can't see chat
Where's chat side to the side? You should be able to check. Okay. Now. I see you. Yeah, see me. It's a great co-host. He's gay
They'll be
I'm a how did you know I'm just ghost ghost is around me ghost
I talk to ghosts all the time. Ghosts is kind of... So, I don't know, but last time I was on...
I went to beat his last night and I saw you backstage, Sigg and stuff, but what happened...
Wait, wait, wait, excuse me. Wait, hold on. Hold on real quick. What do you mean? You saw me backstage?
Because I was like, you know, I was on the show and so I saw you were like talking backstage or something like that
So you were you're you're a co-host on her shim. No, but I just know it's just I could see like
People type being the private chat. That's it. You're tight. You typed in the private chat. I think so. That's how I saw you back there
It was an okay appearance
The psyche you're you're like sharp
Hmm, and so I guess I could just say shout out to you. Oh, thank you
Like you're getting it other people are all retarded right realistically, right?
You're gonna tell me
What you're just saying
I can't imagine why, I don't know. Things usually have a way of explaining themselves and making sense.
If it's not sense, it's nickels, and if it's not nickels, it's dimes. Take that as you will.
Yo, I can't why can't I hear you I
Can't hear you
For some reason I can't hear you
I'm like waiting for you to say something
Well, I can't hear you.
Alright.
Now he's gone.
Cheers, Sean.
Let's say you shot cheers to everyone.
Can't hear you
I don't know, maybe he can't hear me, but if he can, juice. I'm
Merry Chrysler
Juice
Okay, do you hear me now? I do okay. Yes. I hear you just fine
Yeah, so I was gonna say so did you hear the part where I said Sam man was like don't he's like well
Don't you have AIDS to me? I mean he said that can you imagine someone say?
That's like that's like that's such an insanely ridiculous thing to say you're right. Yeah, here's the thing psyche
It's like it's such an insanely ridiculous and disrespectful thing to say
It is so ridiculous and disrespectful that it doesn't even
Warrant the attention right, right? Okay, you can say you can say this is what happened and you're pointing it out
But like do we need to discuss this further?
No, but I mean that was basically a dull thing
I was like just gonna say like what a what a dick
Idiot he was for saying that yeah, this this if this is what this person is gonna say right this person is saying something ridiculous
That's it. Yeah, it's 20 25
And we're expect from him, you know
Like it's 2025 we're going to 2026, right?
The Americas are free fucking country. Okay, you know, if it was a different country, okay
but this is the United States of America and
The fact of the matter is this whether you disagree or agree, right?
What other people do?
Well, like consenting adults do with each other behind closed doors is none of your fucking business
So it's that simple
Simple so unfortunately in history, you know, if we look back at like something like the Stasi in East Germany
Where they had this but that's like how it was before it's not how it is no more
Well, that's how it's becoming right. You're right. You're right. That's how it was
But like it's not like we're in America or at least
I'm saying an ideal right right America it's a free country, right? Okay, so if we have constitutional rights, right?
I'm thinking of the Patriot Act like you know 30 years ago, okay there
I mean the the Patriot Act has no provisions for like these sort of individuality sort of
Yeah, but it kind of like takes away the rights because it has domestic surveillance and that kind of thing where that's for everyone
That's not like a general like specific thing to
It's called the war on terror, right?
And so the war on terror is a very general thing.
It wasn't a war on gays.
You know, I mean, maybe terror is like a code word or something like that,
because there it was there is not a code.
Terror is not a code word for gays.
Well, they can say that gays are and maybe prone to like
violent protests or something like that.
I don't I don't think I don't know if anybody's ever heard of Stonewall.
Have you heard of Stonewall?
these things. Yes, this has happened before, but this is like a rare thing. And I know what you're talking about.
But I'm just saying that this is what people can say as a president. It's kind of like the problem
action resolution, the Hegelian dialect, right? If I'm going to say, here's the thing, I'm not
disagreeing with it, what you're saying, but at the same time, there is sort of like...
a like a degree of a priority, right?
There's like a top priority, lower priority.
But I'm not saying it's a war on gays.
I'm saying it's a war on maybe the American people.
It's like, it's like, it's not a war on gays, specifically.
Of course there's a war on the American people
and facts and real information.
By our own countries, though.
This is a fact, by our own government, of course.
This has always been a thing.
Right since the inception since the very inception of the u.s. Government there has been schemes and sort of corruption
Dissolve the sovereignty of those who deserve the freedom of the rights of being in our country
Right well yeah, but how about like so you're talking about citizens or like you know
You can just say because they have American citizens going to like Guantanamo and stuff right without a trial or whatever
Alligator Island or crocodile island. I don't know what it's called, but right and so there's all these
you know, there's these things that they do instead, right?
Like they'll, they'll, like secretly, right?
And so if you're an American citizen, you have the rights of an American citizen.
Right.
We thought simple.
Ideally, but it's like, you know, it's like, it's not ideally, it's just that simple.
It's just how it should be.
But there, there is a erosion for lack of a better word.
you can you can certainly presume an erosion of these rights
But as things are as things should be
We are assumed certain rights
Say just imagine like if they had the technology that we have today back in the days of the Stasi right where it's like
They would just have like these, you know camera. They had like, you know, I guess they had these these surveillance
cameras according to what I've read and stuff like that, but it seems like
They would have been kind of obvious back then in like the 60s or 70s. They probably
Harder to hide and stuff. I think it would probably be a lot bigger
I think but now we have these tiny little things and we have we have the internet and we have you know all these
And people can have access to things that they're not supposed to have access to and all kinds of thing
there's hackers and blah blah blah blah blah and so
But imagine if they had had I mean imagine how much worse it would have been and it was a disaster for the country like really the Stasi
I'm coming in and then it's like basically they started the informant networks and then it went from just like you know
Okay, so this person might be a you know against the country or something like that too
Just I think like there's like six
people like like for every person there was like six
People assigned to them or something like that or yeah or something like that
I mean did it said that it said this huge thing or for every like six people there was a person assigned to them, right?
Or every black guy they had a hundred white people. It wasn't no it wasn't black
It was it was it was it was in East Germany, so it was all white people pretty much, but I'll say
Um, what happened was then when they started bringing people in, they would say,
okay, well now we'll let you out.
You have to inform on somebody.
Just think they're doing now with the informant system here, right?
Like, okay, well you inform on somebody and who would they inform on?
They would inform on the parents would start informing on the children.
The children would start informing on the parent.
This is parents and children.
This is like really this is either sacred bonds is messing with, right?
And so, um, thank you for what, Gotti?
But anyway, eventually that government was overthrown or whatever, and they went through
and they got all these records released.
Who's messing up the chat?
Who's doing that?
Okay.
Oh, it's Halo.
Okay, don't mind.
Yeah.
Know you might want it but people should really look into like things because then we have you know things like gangstalking and people say
Oh, that's not real. That's not true
And it's like it's it's happened before and it's it's like and yes, it is it is really it is true
I mean it's not a big leap to say. Okay. Well if there's
they're stalkers, we can agree that they're stalkers,
how about if there's groups of them, gang stalkers,
I don't know, it's not too big of a,
it doesn't sound like something that's,
oh, it never happens.
I know there's some people that are just paranoid about it
and some people are, what is it called,
schizophrenic and hear voices and think that there's
helicopters going over their house and stuff like that.
But there's also people that are, like, actively messing with people's minds in order to, like,
let them think that kind of, like, and especially even mentally ill people.
Can you imagine how easy it is to play with mentally ill people's minds in the first place?
They're already off the off kilter, right?
And so, I don't know. I don't know how we got to this conversation.
I was trying to talk about, like, what happened on the thing,
but I was just gonna say one more thing.
Um, yeah, then BlackRG, and I, it's just like,
guys, I'm gonna run the show like I want to run the show.
It's like, if you have, like, feedback about the show and stuff like that.
You can send that to the complaint department at go fuck yourself really really I'm doing the show from for me now
It's like you know, it's like
I mean, I'm doing it for other people too, but it's like I'm not gonna do it if I'm not having fun
I'm not doing what I want to do. I'm doing exactly what I want to do on the show. And so it may not be popular
I mean, but what it's not like I'm like losing a lot of people. I already lost the majority of people, right?
It's like so
So I don't I don't know maybe but then maybe I'll gain the people that actually like are into like what I'm what I'm saying and stuff or like into
me or you know like me instead of this hate watching because I do have seen a lot of just people
wanting to hate watch and document and like oh here's this and then go tell this person and
that this person that and this right so I mean it's like it's just like I don't know since it's
not fun that doesn't make it fun that that's not fun when it's just like a bunch of hate watchers but
there are certain people that that's what they want
Know but I just don't I just don't like it, you know, it's like
Like what I mean? I mean, that's your if that's your discernment and that's your discernment
Yeah, it's just like I asked my personal opinion
And it's like not like I can do anything about it except maybe just like do members only streams and stuff like that
And then just members would go inside and it's like I could do some more of those
I suppose and just like be with people that really really want to watch
Because basically, you know, hey, what's up Mason the drummer? How are you guys doing? Yeah?
So, but anyway, I wasn't really allowed to...
I wasn't really able to talk and then she was like, oh, well, I'm having ghosts at the same time
So he because I want you to have somebody to defend. I'm like, I don't need somebody to defend me
But it's like I but I don't need to be ganged up on by like five people either
But it's like ghost will talk over talk me and stuff like so I was like I believe I just wanted I just wanted to get out my point
last night, but uh
Wasn't really able to I don't think much was much was sorted out. But you know anyway, thanks for having me on the show and you know
Gosh, I don't know it's like
It seems like she's very very set with me and it's like
Well, maybe I'm a little bit of a set with her too over something that happened
But I'm not gonna I'm gonna forget I'm gonna not like hold it over her and say oh
Usually this is I'm a I'm a forgiving person. I'm willing to forgive
But it's not easy to forgive when I'm not forgiven either and so or to change right or there's no incentive to change
It's like you're you're
Just not forgiven, you know, if you're not like
You're just like
You can't, I don't know, I don't know how to express it.
But anyway, it's not talking to you tonight.
Let me see, so I don't know if there's halo
doing skulls in the thing.
Do I have a new drum set?
Oh, I like it, Mason, it looks good.
See, I can't highlight comments.
I don't like that, so that's a major thing
that I can't do that I don't like.
Oh, no, I can't, I can't, look, there it is.
I did it, but it's so big.
Look how big it is, it's covering your whole face.
Where am I? I mean, am I just disappeared? Oh, my camera fell over. Oh my god
I was like, why can't I see myself my camera fellow? I'm so sorry. Okay. Yeah, father's like you in the building. There we go
You know about it. It's an Elysis Nitro Max electronic drum set man
I don't I did I don't I've never heard about it, but I'm not a drummer Mason
And so I'm sure that sounds like one of the better ones, you know, you said it was nice
Good price though, you know, I'm glad you got a drum set because Mason the drummer without a drum set is almost like naked
And as much as I like naked people
I'd rather have you in your clothes
your blue shirt or
Did anybody send you a Star Wars shirt yet Mason? No, okay
Hey, everyone's having fun with the icons that emojis and stuff. So anyway
But anyway, so that was a bit as fine. It was it was kind of a surprise and of course like, you know
And I just want to say like I don't think
Ghost was talking about like giving me $200, you know, I didn't really happen
So, you know, I don't want you to think that I was like, yo, oh, yeah, I just got paid
So that's why I went he didn't donate $200 to me. He said he did just I think just to annoy them or something like that
It's not really a team of streamer Alice if you actually go into the back stage and stuff
It's actually pretty cool. I mean, it's like there's a lot more options and stuff
I don't know if I necessarily need them all. It's just as like it's just as user-friendly
I kind of think it's just as good. Maybe maybe a little bit better than stream
But you know streamers are like a 40 million dollar a year company. I didn't know they were so big. I
Didn't know that they're like
Frickin, you know, that is big. That's pretty big. You know, isn't it? I think it is
Um, let me see. I'm gonna go to my set. I'm gonna see if I can change my banner out. Can you just banner?
Can I? No.
Too late. Too late. Oh here it is. I can. Oh, I got- I made some new logos tonight. See if you guys like it.
Let's see if I have this new logo ready.
Yeah, here. Check this out.
Oh, there it goes. Okay. You see it?
You can hardly see it. It's on the top of the screen. I can I can actually put it up here share presentation
I can't they won't let me present stuff. That sucks. Okay
We all float down here. Yeah, Jamie lives Pennywise I guess
Okay, let me see the layout. Okay. Okay. I can do the layout can change that here. Oh
How do you like it's big like you like it like small like that you're like a big like that
Why can't it go full screen? Oh my gosh. Why can't it go full screen? I don't know why it's not going
All the way. I don't know. I'll figure out later. Yeah, it's interesting. It's interesting
Do I stay at home today? I slept all day. I woke up at probably 6 p.m
In the sun was going down and I went and got two coffees. I still have my coffee from tonight
There's another one of them. I might start drinking some some harder drinks
Jamie has a shirt on oh my god the shirt shirt icons. Why are there really new icons?
So I did stay home today except I didn't go out a little bit
I've been working all afternoon on stuff
And I'm having pretty good time did a lot of mantra and stuff and
Which I've got back into I'm so happy I got back into that if you guys have not tried mantra
Like the real mantra
Like you know in Hinduism like with Sanskrit
It's amazing. It's like it's really really amazing. It's like really really good for your mind and
Plus it's blissful and it's like
Wow, I just has a lot of effects. It has a lot of it has a lot of yeah, I would say
Learn from learn from somebody somebody credible with it, but yeah, it's a
It's a good practice. It's a very good practice. It's very good for mind, controlling your own mind, you know, not mind control, but controlling your own mind.
Because our minds, we're getting so many, we're getting flooded with thoughts. Think about how many thoughts we think in a day, how many, like, a billion, or maybe more, right?
And sometimes some of them are several at times at once and, you know, we have so much coming. Let me see Rudy if he's with me. He's, Rudy's right here.
Well, I'll be careful because I don't, I'm not wearing underwear.
Everyone wants to see Rudy. Mr. Rude. Okay, there you go
You see SIG? Say hi to SIG. He's making a face at SIG. No
That's Rudy
The cats are cats are all good. Let's see Lola's right there. I think Trix is outside and the nor was just here, but
I think she's outside now, too. So it's a calm. It was actually a nice day and it's the holiday season
Um, I do like the holidays like December you see
Yo play this for your cats see if they like it and then I don't play music. Hey, don't just put stuff up with that talking to me
Stop it yourself
Okay, that's it dude, chill out, what the fuck?
No, I wasn't even talking to the stream, I can't have copyrights.
You're all like crashing out of shit bro, what the fuck?
Because, I can't have copyrights.
You're all freaking out bro, what the fuck?
Because first of all, you didn't ask, second of all.
Bro, you're all freaking out, what do you mean I didn't ask?
You clicked the button.
I didn't click anything, it went right up.
You clicked, oh you didn't?
I didn't click it, no.
Mean I don't know
You set it up like that you
You set it up like that you say your shit to like automatically play everything
You fucking set it up like that it's not my fault fucking retard fuck
Fuck is the matter with you
It's just our retarded. What do you like? What is the shit?
Out this shit sucks
Stream yard there you go. You don't even know
I'm immune to your mic. That's good enough
You don't even know how to kick me out. This just sucks
This is
You don't even know stop you don't even know how to kick me out. This just sucks. You're retarded fuck this shit
Fuck this shit. You don't even know how to kick me out. What the fuck fuck this shit